[Music] Do you
[Música]
understand me Javi? It was not even possible to verify
me entiendes Javi No se pudo comprobar
the payment in kind, of course,
ni siquiera el pago por especies claro
no, it cannot be proven. Of course, well, there was
no que no se puede demostrar Claro pues
no evidence, that's why they were
hecho no hay había indicios por eso lo
investigating him, just as there are evidence
investigaban igual que hay indicios
now of the revelation of a secret, and now
ahora de revelación de secreto y ahora
that will be played out, but here in this country,
eso se jugará pero aquí en este país
in order to be convicted, you have to prove the
para que condenen tienes que probar la
criminal charge and the criminal charge of a
carga penal y la carga penal de una
revelation of a secret. On the part of the
revelación de Secreto yo por parte de la
TV factory,
fábrica de la tele
I think it's going to be civil, not criminal. And if
yo creo que va a ser civil no penal Y si
anything, eh. Because then you have to see
acaso eh Porque luego tienes que ver
each character
cada cada personaje que es lo que ha
to see what they got from each character. Let's see. I see the
sacado de cada personaje a ver yo veo
Isa pixido case as serious, but serious,
grave lo de lo de Isa pixido pero grave
for example, but I don't know if that's
por ejemplo pero es que no sé si eso
prescribed. No, the thing about leaving on foot was
está prescrito no lo de irse a pie era
that she had gone to the Fátima hospital, no, and
que había ido al hospital de Fátima no y
that she had bled, that she had had an
que había sangrado que había tenido un
abortion, which was in the report. I
aborto que tenía en el parte eso yo lo
see that as serious, no matter how much you sell your
veo grave por mucho que tú vendas tu
life, because the fact that you sell your
vida porque el hecho de que tú vendas tu
life doesn't mean you don't have the right to
vida tampoco es que no tengas derecho a
privacy, if you do, what happens is
la intimidad si lo tienes lo que pasa
that it's broader, but for example, that they
que es más amplio pero por ejemplo que
get a report from you, that you go to a
saquen un parte tuyo que tú vayas a un
doctor.  and they take out the part that has
médico y te saquen ahí el parte que ha
bled I don't know how much I do see that as
sangrado no sé cuánto eso sí lo veo
condemnable but it is civil
condenable pero es civil
Of course but we We apart we don't
Claro pero nosotros Nosotros aparte no
know
sabemos
what is in the investigation
lo que hay en la investigación
[Music]
[Música]
the Remember that the police that it all
la Acuérdate que la policía que todo
started So the number of celebrities is
empezó O sea que el número de famosos se
known because they entered Gustavo's house
sabe porque entraron en la casa de
and he had everything well filed
Gustavo y lo tenía todo bien archivadito
on a computer So we don't
en un ordenador Entonces nosotros no
know if on that computer or in what
sabemos si en ese ordenador o en lo que
the police have found there is also
han encontrado la policía también hay
evidence that you really do pass
pruebas de que realmente sí le pasas a
the information to Sálvame or to the
la información a sálvame o a la fábrica
TV factory you know what I want to tell you
de la tele sabes lo que te quiero decir
just as there was information about
igual que hay que había información de
celebrities all organized by folders and
famosos todo ordenadito por carpetitas y
by things you will see if you did not have
por cositas veré tú a saber si no tenía
WhatsApp web open or I don't know you
abierto el WhatsApp web o yo que sé
know what I want to tell you and
sabes lo que te quiero decir y no ha
that information has not transcended because
trascendido esa información porque
logically their line of investigation
lógicamente su línea de investigación
of course There are things that maybe it says no they have not
claro Hay cosas que a lo mejor dice no
released the sentence well the
han sacado la sentencia bueno la
sentence or the medical report what the
sentencia o el parte médico lo que la
sensitive information on screen but
información sensible en pantalla pero
the investigators have the data that
los investigadores tienen los datos que
proves that they have passed it to the
prueban que sí que se lo han pasado a la
TV factory and they have been freed from
fábrica de la tele y se ha Librado de
bribery because  They have nothing to prove
cohecho porque no tienen nada que pruebe
that the other guy has collected money, Paola says,
Que ha cobrado dinero el otro dice Paola
the crime of discovery and disclosure
el delito de descubrimiento y revelación
of secrets is well tied up, but for the
de secretos está bien atado pero para el
police officer, Paola, or for everyone
policía Paola o para todos
because for everyone, that
porque para todos
is, for the program
o sea para el programa
that has published, for example, the program. I do
que ha publicado por ejemplo el programa
n't remember specifically now,
Yo es que ahora en concreto no no
but of course
recuerdo pero es que claro
the program has published it, but the
que ha publicado el programa pero el
issue is, the issue is that if they have
tema es el tema es que si le han
charged him, it will be for something. The
imputado será por algo Los
investigators,
investigadores
luckily, that's how our country works,
por suerte así funciona nuestro país
but what I want to tell you is that they will
pero que lo que te quiero decir es que
have something solid so that the game has been
tendrán algo sólido para que el juego se
rejected, just like bribery,
lo haya rechazo igual que el cohecho
then it has to be. And if they have
entonces tiene que ser Y si ellos han
taken and called 150 celebrities or
cogido y han llamado a 150 famosos o los
whatever, 140 or so, after obtaining
que sean 140 y pico después de obtener
what I'm telling you, the record of Gustavo
lo que te digo el registro de Gustavo
González, then logically there will be something there
González pues lógicamente habrá algo ahí
that is an annex of the Union with the
que sea anexo de Unión con la fábrica de
television factory, otherwise they would have been freed and it would
la tele sino ya se habrían Librado y
only be Gustavo and the police officer.
solo estaría Gustavo y el policía
In any case, it is still unknown
de todas maneras todavía no se sabe
who will sit in the dock,
quiénes van a sentarse en el banquillo
right? Now they are
no eh Ahora se está esperando
still waiting for the defendants that were there, they are not
todavía los imputados que había no son
definitive at this moment because now they have to
definitivos en este momento porque ahora
wait for the order that reopens the
hay que esperar el auto que reabra el
trial. In other words, it puts the  trial date
juicio O sea que pone la fecha de juicio
for the police and Gustavo González
para los policías y Gustavo González
Regarding the producers I still don't know,
Respecto a los productores aún no lo sé
Paola says Paola thinks I think that for
dice opina Paola Paola Yo opino que para
the production company it's that Gustavo
la productora es que Gustavo
and the police officer here are safe because you
y el policía acá en seguro porque tú
Although no although Gustavo Imagine if he
Aunque no aunque Gustavo Imagínate que
hadn't done business with the
no hubiese comercializado con la fábrica
TV factory and nothing you can't have
de la tele y nada tú no puedes tener en
personal data on your computer
tu ordenador datos personales fichas
police records medical records of 150
policiales fichas médicas de 150
people
personas
they'll catch them Well the thing is
te las pillan Pues
Gustavo went overboard one
es que Gustavo Se pasó de la raya una
thing is that you have something
cosa es que tú tengas en un momento algo
to break the news for at one point another thing is that
para dar la noticia por otra cosa es que
you have your own and from what
tú tengas tu propio y por lo que
transpired he had
trascendió lo tenía
your own Arsenal of course that might be
tu propio Arsenal claro eso lo mismo es
going a bit too far Okay guys we're going to get really
pasarse un poco Bueno chicos nos vamos a
angry she's not
ir a la neta enfadado no
angry
está enfadada
with the two of you because you're passing around photos of
con los dos porque vais pasando fotos
me
mías
[Music]
[Música]
Graduate in labor relations those
graduado en relaciones laborales esos
are in another karaoke room
están en otra sala de karaoke
my opinion is that I think what's going to
yo es mi opinión que yo creo que va a
happen okay it's going to
pasar vale
be an incredible scandal what about if
que sea un escándalo increíble lo de si
the TV factory is released buff I
la fábrica de la tele se Libra buff yo
think listen it's not going to be that much of a
creo escucha tampoco va a ser tanto
scandal because the truth is we
escándalo porque en verdad nosotros nos
think that  all of Spain knows why
pensamos que lo sabe toda España porque
we're involved here in the chronicle
estamos metidos aquí en el en la crónica
and really if Antena 3 doesn't say anything
tal y Realmente si Antena 3 no dice nada
if Spanish television doesn't say anything if
si televisión española no dice nada si
the magazine doesn't say anything nobody knows why do
la revista no dice nada nadie lo sabe
we think it's
para que nosotros nos pensamos que es
super important you know why don't they say
súper importante sabes por qué no dicen
anything because
nada porque
what are you going to say that Telecinco
qué es lo que vas a decir que telecinco
had police sources that gave you
tenía Fuentes policiales que te daban
information about this in front of the other because if we
datos de estos ante el otro porque si
start with that now another one takes it and says
empezamos con esa ahora coge otro y dice
yes like your police source is the policeman
sí como tu fuente policial es el policía
from Alcobenda who I don't know what good
de ahí de alcobenda que no sé qué bueno
participated in programs with María Patiño
participó en programas con María Patiño
and all the people on Antena 3 or so
y toda la gente en la Antena 3 o sea
yes
que sí
apart is what I'm telling you So if they
aparte es lo que te digo O sea que que
start with that to throw themselves at each
si empiezan con esas a tirarse entre
other then of course now another one takes it and says
ellos pues claro ahora coge otro y dice
Well you have a doctor there at the
Pues tú tienes un médico ahí en el
Macarena Well you have another doctor there
Macarena Pues tú tienes otro médico ahí
at the Fátima Well you have another one there you
en el Fátima Pues tú tienes otro ahí
know what it is that we're not going to see anything I
sabes que es que nada vamos a ver yo
can I can as a journalist even
puedo yo puedo como periodista incluso
almost as a medium eh have my Sources what
casi como medio eh tener mi Fuentes lo
you can't publish is true
que tú no puedes publicar es cierto
content that violates privacy okay
contenido que vulnere la intimidad vale
But now one thing is that I have that
Pero ahora una cosa es que yo tenga ese
right or  that I do it that way
derecho o que yo lo haga de esa manera
doing things right and another thing is
haciendo las cosas bien y otra cosa es
that I go collecting and I keep
que yo vaya cogiendo y me vaya guardando
in a computer or in a hard drive
en un ordenador o en un disco duro lo
whatever here as if it were this another
que sea aquí como si fuera esto otro
police file or or the Sas No here everything
fichero policial o o el Sas No aquí todo
full of medical records and I have here
lleno de fichas médicas y tengo yo aquí
the medical history of the famous ones I
la el historial médico de los famosos
understand that that is where the
entiendo que ahí es donde tiene el
problem is Gustavo González yes yes he had
problema Gustavo González si si tenía
everything stored Well of course about pipi you are
todo almacenado Pues claro de pipi estás
talking about intimate videos of I don't know what
hablaban de vídeos íntimos de no sé qué
of I don't know how much but of course it will
de no sé cuánto pero claro
depend on the issue of Gustavo it will depend
dependerá el tema de Gustavo dependerá
within the within what he had
dentro de los dentro de lo que tuviera
on the computer of what those
en el ordenador de lo que los propios
affected do for example
afectados hagan por ejemplo
Imagine that imagine that Gustavo
Imagínate que imagínate que Gustavo
had on the computer about Paula
tenía en el ordenador sobre Paula
Echevarría a
Echevarría
medical report that she had a headache he
parte médico de que le dolía la cabeza
says I'm not going to condemn you for this
dice yo por esto no te voy a condenar
outside I'm working on sacks
fuera me estoy trabajando en costales
better
mejor
Imagine that about Chabelita you have what they
Imagínate que sobre Chabelita tienes lo
released that medical report and it says
que sacaron parte médico ese y dice
Chabelita I am in survivor and
Chabelita Yo estoy en superviviente y
right now I have not done I do not get involved
ahora mismo yo no he hecho no me meto
outside
fuera
the revelation of the secret what it
el la revelación del secreto lo que
has is that the people involved
tiene es que las personas implicadas
have to want that now they have a
tienen que querer que ahora tengan un
video of Alba Carrillo who is also there,
vídeo de Alba Carrillo que están también
passing I don't know well
está personada ahí pasando no sé bien
with Marta López and Jorge Pérez on the couch
con Marta López y Jorge Pérez en el sofá
No look here is the here is the here
No mira aquí está la aquí está la aquí
is the photo eh eye of the ring what you
está la foto eh ojo del anillo que tú
say Look Yes look they have passed
dices Mira Sí mira han pasado
the ring to the right May 2021 with
el anillo a la derecha mayo de 2021 con
the ring let's see
el anillo que a ver
[ __ ] today today today today today today I
ostias hoy hoy hoy hoy hoy hoy
told you I told you I told you
he dicho te lo he dicho te lo he dicho
all the carrasquistas at full speed wide wide
todas las carrasquistas a tope amplia
wide Investigate
amplia amplia Investiga
Well here I see a ring
Bueno yo aquí veo un anillo
the same color you
el mismo color
have to tell me that they are there, let's
me tiene que decir tú que están ellos
see with the other one
a ver con el otro
but let's see let's see let's see or rather
pero a ver a ver a ver a ver o sea
really Here What is the conflict if
realmente Aquí Cuál es el conflicto si
she already said in the
ella ya dijo en el en el directo de
Caris live that while Olga was in
caris que mientras Olga estaba en
Survivors she had been
supervivientes ella había sido
but the story that what I read which
pero la historia que lo que leído yo que
is what you have not heard before is that there are
es lo que no has escuchado antes que es
people who say that the ring
que hay gente que dice que el anillo
has photos from 2016 of 2015 we
tiene en fotos de 2016 de 2015
are seeing each other many years ago not
nos estamos viendo muchos años atrás no
because of that what I was telling him that is what is being
por eso lo que lo que le comentaba a él
released there on
que es lo que se está soltando ahí por
Twitter let's see here Leo You believe  that they're going to be
Twitter a ver aquí Leo Tú te crees que
together for eight years and they've been
van a llevar ocho años juntos y llevan
since I mean if the rings of 2015-2016
desde O sea si el anillos del 2015-2016
and Mars was going to be silent for 8 years come on
y Marte iba a estar 8 años callada venga
man please for me the most
hombre por favor para mí la historia más
emotional story and with this we're going to close
emotiva y con esto vamos a cerrar
directly because this is a life advice has
directo porque esto es un consejo de
been this I don't know if you've seen it
ha sido esta no sé si la habéis visto
okay but Marta risco
vale pero Marta risco
hashtag things to do when you've
hashtag cosas que hacer cuando has
lost almost everything okay And she's
perdido casi todo vale Y está
writing one the tips Some notes and
escribiendo una las puntas Unas notas y
writes things to do when you've
pone cosas que hacer cuando lo has
lost almost everything
perdido casi todo
okay it
vale
sounds dramatic but really Marta
suena dramático pero realmente que Marta
risco right now has lost almost
risco ahora mismo lo ha perdido casi
everything she's lost love she's lost her
todo ha perdido el amor ha perdido el
job things to do
trabajo cosas que hacer
for real
de verdad
a lamp put the tips of my hair
una lámpara ponerme las puntas del pelo
pink no joke eh No joke eh put
Rosa no es coña eh No es coña eh ponerme
the tips of my hair pink
las puntas del pelo Rosa
but they are messages from her that this
pero que son mensajes suyos que esta
girl It's not that she's 15 years old
chiquilla No es que tiene 15 años
mentally she
mentales
sits with her with her fuchsia pen
se pone con su con su boli fucsia
write fuchsia things but this so
escribir cosas fucsias pero esto para
that she knows how to provoke people no
que esto lo sepa provocar a la gente no
Of course but then you have to read the
Claro pero luego le tienes que leer
comments When you make a video that
comentarios Cuando haces un vídeo que te
tells you no but it's that but what imagination do
dice no pero es que pero qué imaginación
you say but know  Please, I think you do
tienes digo pero saber por favor creo
n't know what context we're in. I
que no sabéis En qué contexto estamos O
mean, man, things to do when you
sea que tío cosas que hacer cuando lo
've lost everything. Of course, in a super
has perdido todo Claro en plan súper
dramatic way, it's missing the sad music and
dramática le falta la música triste y
now it says, "Put the tips of my hair
ahora pone ponerme las puntas del pelo
pink"
rosa
and the other day with the song "She was putting on
y el otro día con la canción Se estaba
makeup but going to a party and just
maquillando pero irse de fiesta y justo
when they stop, a nose," the song was "You were
cuando dejan de una nariz la canción era
looking for me to kiss me secretly You were
me buscabas para besarme a escondidas me
looking for me to devour me secretly."
buscabas para devorarme a escondidas
Well, who is the song for? For my
pues para quién va la canción para mi
cousin, watch out,
prima
people are applauding your
ojo que te está aplaudiendo la gente al
acne. People are with you and
acné la gente está contigo y con
not with us.
nosotros no
[Music]
[Música]